

About Me

I was a Pastry Chef / Cook for 7 years, until transitioning to the UX Design field.

My goal is to solve problems using Human Centered Design principles, designing accessible digital products, providing a pleasing and satisfying experiences for.

I'm a very hard worker, creative, a team player, I easely adapt to any environment or situation and I'm never afraid to express my feelings and ideas at any moment.

Info



Berlin, Germany



+351 917 151 823



g.estevesferreira@gmail.com



in/gestevesf

Skills

User Research Personas User Flows User Journeys Sketching Wireframing Prototyping User Testing Style Guides HTML CSS JavaScript

Tools











Gonçalo Esteves Ferreira

UX Designer

Projects

Sneaker Help

Mobile Web-Application, Feb 2021 - Sep 2021

Conducted competitive analysis, user interviews and user testing. Defined user personas and MVP document. Performed sketching and designed from Low to High-Fidelity wireframes and a interactive prototype.

OSICA

Business Project, Aug 2020 - present

I'm responsible for the creation of the brand, management of stock, web design, marketing strategy, sustainable operations and productions activities.

Work Experience

OSICA

Founder, Aug 2020 - Present

Founded the brand, designed the product, built the production process, managed suppliers and developed the website and marketing strategy.

Wonderbly

Customer Servive, Oct 2018 - Present

I'm responsible for repling and resolving customers tickets in English and Portuguese, translate and check grammar in books from English books to Portuguese and also check the quality control on books printed and deliever within Germany.

Soho House, Berlin

Pastry Chef, Jul 2019 - Jul 2020

I was responsible for having products well confectioned and presented while maintaining consistency. Completing daily tasks, management of stock and inventory, HACCP regulations in the pastry and supporting Chef with new ideas for recipes.

Lekker; Le Moulin de Connelles; Nithan Thai; Mrs. Robinson; Pestana Hotel

Cook & Pastry Chef, Jul 2014 - Jul 2019

I was responsible for the confection of products and recipes, management of stock and inventory, HACCP regulations in the kitchen, supporting Chefs with new ideas for recipes and was responsible for the service in Pastry and Kitchen areas.

Education

Web Development Specialization

CareerFoundry, Current

UX Design BootcampCareerFoundry, 2021

Pastry Diploma Le Cordon Bleu, 2016

Languages

Mother Tongue

Portuguese

Fluent

English, Spanish

Conversational

French

Basic

German